<Document>
 # SS14 Server Rules – Kepler Station
RP Levels Defined
MRP – Medium Roleplay (Default):
Players are expected to act semi-realistically and stay in-character most of the time. Humor and creativity are allowed but should not break immersion or disrupt gameplay. You are still part of a functioning space station with a chain of command.

HRP+ – High Roleplay Plus (Special Events):
High-level character immersion is expected. Players should have consistent personalities, motivations, and behave realistically. Breaking character or doing “for the lulz” actions is not acceptable. HRP+ is reserved for curated rounds and events.

LRP+ – Light Roleplay Plus (Casual Rounds):
A bit more relaxed. Mildly silly behavior is tolerated as long as it doesn’t ruin the round or disrupt others. This is still not NRP — random killings, griefing, or nonsense are not allowed.

## 1. Respect Others
Treat other players with basic respect. No harassment, slurs, hate speech, or personal attacks. Roleplay conflict is fine, personal conflict is not.

## 2. Stay In Character
Your character must act believably. They should behave as a person in their job would. Avoid breaking character for memes, OOC jokes, or trolling.

## 3. No Self-Antagging
Don’t act like an antagonist unless the game gives you the role. This includes random killing, sabotage, setting fires, releasing plasma, etc.

## 4. Antagonists Must RP
If you are an antagonist, you still have to roleplay. Your actions must have some kind of believable context or reasoning — not just a killing spree.

## 5. Metagaming is Forbidden
You cannot use OOC (out-of-character) knowledge to give your character an advantage. Don’t act on information your character couldn’t possibly know.

## 6. No Powergaming
Don’t hoard weapons or high-end gear just because you can. Play your role — a janitor shouldn’t be wearing riot gear "just in case."

## 7. No Griefing
Ruining the round for others with no RP justification is considered griefing. This includes spacing the station, stealing vital gear, or killing innocents for fun.

## 8. Appropriate Character Names
Use proper, realistic names. No meme names ("Sus Amogus", "Big Chungus"), references, joke names, or offensive content. Admins will rename or remove bad characters.

## 9. No Erotic Roleplay (ERP)
ERP is strictly prohibited under all circumstances. Even suggestive behavior or jokes that cross the line will result in punishment.

## 10. No OOC in IC
Don’t use out-of-character chat in in-character channels. Use OOC (/ooc) or Discord for that. Don’t say things like “brb” or “lag” in character.

## 11. Use of Bugs and Exploits
If you find a bug or exploit, report it. Don’t use it to gain an advantage. Exploiting can result in bans.

## 12. Do Not Spam or Micspam
No chat flooding, soundboard abuse, or repeated messages. Use radio channels appropriately and don’t make IC communication unusable.

## 13. Follow Admin Instructions
Admins have the final word. If you are told to stop something, stop. If you disagree, use proper appeal channels — not arguments in-game.

## 14. Respect the Atmosphere
This is a roleplay server. Treat it like a real station — not a playground. Don’t go around screaming, smashing things, or being a chaotic mess unless that fits your role (and is done well).
</Document>
